Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 8 and District 8 Locals, 1936-1957 UE.4.1.8
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 8 Locals, 2.
  - Local 805
    - Local 805 Newspaper Clippings, November 16, 1945 - March 5, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 92)
      - "Resolution," Tell City News, November 16, 1945; 1.
      - "Tell City Plant Workers Stage Token Walkout," Evansville Courier, March 5, 1946; 2.
    - Local 805 Organization, May 16 - June 23, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 93)
      - Mary Swart to Bill, May 16, 1944; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Swart, May 21, 1944; 2.
      - Emspak to William Sentner, May 21, 1944; 3.
      - James Payne to Emspak, June 23, 1944; 4.
    - Local 805 Strike, November 13 - December 1945 (Box 3, Folder 94)
      - Julius Emspak to James Payne, November 13, 1945; 1.
      - Letter to Albert Fitzgerald, November 15, 1945; 2.
      - Termination of Strike Notice, November 21, 1945; 3.
      - War Labor Board Recommendation, December 1945; 4.
    - Local 805 Factionalism and Burden Subsidy, February 8 - May 28, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 95)
      - Charles Rosenbaum to William Sentner, February 8, 1948; 1.
      - James Matles to Sentner, March 3, 1948; 2.
      - Matles to Rosenbaum, March 3, 1948; 3.
      - Matles to Rosenbaum, March 12, 1948; 4.
      - Robert Logsden to Matles, May 28, 1948; 5.
    - Local 805 IUE Inter-union Rivalry, December 16, 1949 - April 24, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 96)
      - Otto Maschoff to James Matles, December 16, 1949; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Maschoff, December 20, 1949; 2.
      - Maschoff to Emspak, December 29, 1949; 3.
      - Emspak to Maschoff, February 10, 1950; 4.
      - Lou Kimmel to Emspak, April 24, 1950; 5.
    - Local 805 Correspondence, December 20, 1944 - October 12, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 97)
      - Jacob Hoffman to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, December 20, 1944; 1.
      - Interim Grievance Procedures, 1944; 2.
      - Irene Huck to William Sentner Regarding Organization with May 22, 1945, Sentner Letter to Morris Muster, May 19, 1945; 3.
      - Otto Maschoff to James Matles Regarding Negotiations with Maschoff Letter to Louis Schwellenbach, October 12, 1946; 4.
  - Local 806
    - Local 806 Officers List, April 7 - December 8, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Local 806 Incoming Correspondence, June 6, 1946 - March 30, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 99)
      - Julius Emspak to Ada Masters Regarding Dues and Veterans, June 6, 1946; 1.
      - Emspak to Milford Seabough Regaridng Per Capita, January 17, 1947; 2.
      - Emspak to Carrie McLain Regarding Finances, May 19, 1947; 3.
      - Emspak to Lindell Pind Regarding Per Capita, January 7, 1948; 4.
      - Emspak to Kenneth Break Regarding Per Capita, February 18, 1948; 5.
      - Emspak to James Crader Regarding Finances, March 30, 1948; 6.
    - Local 806 Outgoing Correspondence, June 6, 1947 - November 17, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 100)
      - Clyde Cook to Julius Emspak Regarding Officers, November 18, 1947; 1.
      - James Newcomer to UE Regarding Per Capita, November 17, 1948; 2.
      - Nora Teaford to Emspak, June 6, 1947; 3.
    - Local 806 Organization and Strike, April 1946 (Box 3, Folder 101)
      - Julius Emspak to William Sentner, April 23, 1946; 1.
      - Emspak to Otto Maschoff, April 23, 1946; 2.
      - Otto Mashoff Letter, April 25, 1946; 3.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement, April 25, 1946; 4.
      - Brief History of Local 806, April 1946; 5.
    - Local 806 Strike Report and Termination Notice, May 1 - June 5, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Local 806 Correspondence, July 5, 1946 - April 16, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 103)
      - Charles Anderson to James Matles Regarding Finances, July 5, 1946; 1.
      - Termination of Strike, October 2, 1946; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to Robert Logsden Regarding Membership, November 23, 1948; 3.
      - Logsden to Matles Regarding International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, April 16, 1949; 4.
      - William Sentner to Emspak Regarding Strikes, Undated; 5.
  - Local 808 (St. Louis)
    - Local 808 (St. Louis) Correspondence, Julius Emspak to E. Tahy Regarding Organization, October 29, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Local 808 (St. Louis) Charter Applicaiton, October 4, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Local 808 (Henderson)
    - Local 808 (Henderson) Correspondence, Julius Emspak to James David, March 18, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Local 808 (Henderson) Organization and Disbanding, February - May 2, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 107)
      - Otto Maschoff to Julius Emspak, February 1947; 1.
      - Emspak to Maschoff, March 1947; 2.
      - Emspak to William Sentner, March 18, 1947; 3.
      - Charter Supplies, March 18, 1947; 4.
      - Emspak to Sentner, March 31, 1947; 5.
      - Maschoff to Emspak, May 2, 1947; 6.
  - Local 808 (Evansville)
    - Local 808 (Evansville) Officers List, September 23, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - Local 808 (Evansville) Correspondence, Julius Emspak to Leroy Bartley Regarding Separate Charter, October 13, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Local 808 (Evansville) Publications, December 1951 - April 1952 (Box 3, Folder 110)
      - Radio Script Regarding Stirke and Inter-union Rivalry, December 9, 1951; 1.
      - Newspaper Clipping "Union Ends Strike at Seeger Plant", December 1951; 2.
      - "Membership Meeting" Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, April 1952; 3.
    - Local 808 (Evansville) Separate Charter, Octrober 1949 (Box 3, Folder 111)
      - Julius Emspak to Joseph Pogue, October 13, 1949; 1.
      - Emspak to William Sentner, October 13, 1949; 2.
  - Local 809
    - Local 809 Officers List, October 2, 1941 - August 26, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Local 809 Incoming Correspondence, August 3, 1938 - June 23, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 113)
      - Julius Emspak to Rufus Payne Regarding Organization, August 3, 1938; 1.
      - Emspak to R. Payne Regarding Organization, August 4, 1938; 2.
      - Emspak to R. Payne Regarding 1938 UE Convention, August 29, 1938; 3.
      - Emspak to R. Payne Regarding Unemployment, August 30, 1938; 4.
      - Emspak to Irene Payne Regarding Supplies, October 4, 1938; 5.
      - Emspak to I. Payne Regarding UE Constitution, November 9, 1938; 6.
      - Emspak to R. Payne Regarding Address, November 18, 1938; 7.
      - Emspak to Ralph Omdahl Regarding Per Capita, November 22, 1938; 8.
      - Emspak to R. Payne Regarding CIO, January 13, 1939; 9.
      - Emspak to R. Payne Regarding Dues, January 26, 1939; 10.
      - Emspak to Omdahl Regarding Dues with Show-up Slip, January 23, 1939; 11.
      - Emspak to James Stefani Regarding CIO and Finances, April 4, 1939; 12.
      - Emspak to Stefani Regarding Local 809 Constitution, May 11, 1939; 13.
      - Emspak to R. Payne Regarding Membership, December 4, 1939; 14.
      - Emspak to Dale Schweibert Regarding Seniority, July 18, 1940; 15.
      - Emspak to Schwiebert Regarding Negotiations, September 21, 1940; 16.
      - Emspak to Schwiebert Regarding Financial Reports, October 7, 1940; 17.
      - Emspak to Byron Gray Regarding Finances, October 28, 1941; 18.
      - Emspak to Floyd Katzenberger Regarding Dues, June 23, 1943; 19.
      - Emspak to Cecilia Trumbla Regarding Finances, August 4, 1944; 20.
      - Emspak to Trumbla Regarding Finances, February 6, 1945; 21.
      - Emspak to Trumbla Regarding Finances, December 11, 1946; 22.
    - Local 809 Incoming Correspondence, 1939, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 114)
      - Julius Emspak to Cecelia Trumbla Regarding Per Capita, January 7, 1947; 1.
      - Emspak to Trumbla Regarding Finances, May 12, 1947; 2.
      - James Matles to James Stefani Regarding Wages, January 17, 1939; 3.
      - J.S. Steckley to Stefani Regarding Wages, August 24, 1939; 4.
    - Local 809 Outgoing Correspondence, September 10, 1941 - July 28, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 115)
      - Byron Gray to UE Regarding Officers, September 10, 1941; 1.
      - Gray to Julius Emspak Regarding Supplies, October 23, 1941; 2.
      - Robert Karnes to UE Regarding Officers, May 4, 1944; 3.
      - Floyd Katzenberger to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, June 14, 1943; 4.
      - Ralph Omdahl to Emspak Regarding Officers, October 16, 1938; 5.
      - Omdahl to Emspak Regarding Unemployment, January 11, 1939; 6.
      - Omdahl to Emspak Regarding Dues, January 11, 1939; 7.
      - Omdahl to Emspak Regarding Officers and Per Capita, May 14, 1942; 8.
      - Irene Payne to Emspak Regarding Finances, September 29, 1938; 9.
      - Rufus Payne to Emspak Regarding UE Convention, August 22, 1938; 10.
      - R. Payne to Emspak Regarding Finances, August 22, 1938; 11.
      - R. Payne to Emspak Regarding Officers, December 18, 1938; 12.
      - R. Payne to Emspak Regarding Dues, January 21, 1939; 13.
      - R. Payne to Emspak Regarding Officers, NOvember 21, 1939; 14.
      - James Stefani to James Matles Regarding Wages, January 14, 1939; 15.
      - Stefani to Emspak Regarding Wages, August 7, 1939; 16.
      - Stefani to Emspak Regarding Contract, October 5, 1939; 17.
      - Dale Schwiebert to Emspak Regarding Negotiations, July 11, 1940; 18.
      - Schwiebert to Emspak Regarding Negotiations, October 5, 1940; 19.
      - Schwiebert to Emspak Regarding Officers, October 5, 1940; 20.
      - Harold Swartfager to Emspak Regarding Officers, January 1941; 21.
      - Cecelia Trumbla to UE Regarding Finances, July 28, 1944; 22.
    - Local 809 Receipts, August 4 - 26, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Local 809 Per Capita, August 19, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Local 809 Leaflet, "Notice" Regarding Unemployment, November 9, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Local 809 CIO Transfer and Union Lables, June 7 - August 2, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 119)
      - Charter Application, June 7, 1938; 1.
      - William Sentner to John Brophy, June 8, 1938; 2.
      - Sentner to Julius Emspak, June 8, 1938; 3.
      - D.M. Bridges to Don Harris, July 22, 1938; 4.
      - Sentner to Emspak, July 26, 1938; 5.
      - Sentner to Emspak, August 2, 1938; 6.
  - Local 810
    - Local 810 Officers Lists, December 29, 1939 - April 19, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Local 810 Membership Resolutions, October 2, 1942 - August 1946 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Resolution Regarding Organization with October 3, 1942, Herman Steinkoetter Letter to James Matles, October 2, 1942; 1.
      - Resolution Regarding Factionalism, August 1946; 2.
    - Local 810 Incoming Correspondence, July 11, 1941 - July 21, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Julius Emspak to Walter Rapp Regarding Constitution, July 11, 1941; 1.
      - Emspak to Rapp Regarding Bonding, September 28, 1943; 2.
      - Emspak to Rapp Regarding Dues and Veterans, January 23, 1945; 3.
      - Emspak to Clarence Bingaman Regarding Per Capita, November 8, 1946; 4.
      - Emspak to Rapp Regarding Finances, November 21, 1946; 5.
      - Emspak to Rapp Regarding Finances, December 2, 1946; 6.
      - Emspak to Rapp Regarding Finances, December 9, 1946; 7.
      - Emspak to Rapp Regarding Finances, December 19, 1946; 8.
      - Emspak to Rapp Regarding Political Action Committee, January 7, 1948; 9.
      - Emspak to Bingaman Regarding Per Capita, March 16, 1948; 10.
      - Emspak to Bingaman Regarding Per Capita, August 3, 1950; 11.
      - Emspak to Bingaman Regarding Per Capita, February 26, 1951; 12.
      - Emspak to Bingaman Regarding UE News, March 17, 1952; 13.
      - Emspak to Bingaman Regarding Loyd-Scrugs, April 29, 1952; 14.
      - Emspak to Bingaman Regarding UE Convention, July 30, 1952; 15.
      - Emspak to Rapp Regarding UE Fighting Fund, October 15, 1952; 16.
      - Emspak to Bingaman Regarding UE Fighting Fund, October 23, 1952; 17.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Bingaman Regarding Raid-baiting, July 21, 1952; 18.
      - James Matles to Rapp Regarding Finances, January 8, 1943; 19.
      - Matles to Bingaman Regarding Organization, December 14, 1945; 20.
      - David Ratner to Bingaman Regarding Social Security, December 19, 1946; 21.
    - Local 810 Outgoing Correspondence, March 30, 1942 - July 28, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Clarence Bingaman to Julius Emspak Regarding Officers, June 24, 1943; 1.
      - Bingaman to Emspak Regaridng Per Capita, October 31, 1945; 2.
      - Bingaman to James Matles Regarding Organization, November 28, 1945; 3.
      - Bingaman to Emspak Regarding Bonding, March 27, 1946; 4.
      - Bingaman to Nat Spero Regarding Negotiations, August 7, 1946; 5.
      - Bingaman to Emspak Regarding Local 825, December 9, 1946; 6.
      - Bingaman to William Sentner Regarding Factionalism, March 13, 1947; 7.
      - Bingaman to J.N. Dazey Regarding Negotiations, September 18, 1947; 8.
      - Bingaman to Missouri Department of Labor Regarding Strikes, November 18, 1947; 9.
      - Bingaman to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, March 26, 1948; 10.
      - Bingaman to Emspak Regarding Supplies, Novebmer 7, 1949; 11.
      - Bingaman to Emspak Regarding Finances, July 31, 1950; 12.
      - Bingaman to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, Februayr 20, 1951; 13.
      - Bingaman to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Red-baiting, June 4, 1951; 14.
      - Bingaman to Fitzgerald Regarding Red-baiting, July 17, 1951; 15.
      - Bingaman to Emspak Regarding UE News, March 3, 1952; 16.
      - Bingaman to Emspak Regarding UE Convention, July 28, 1952; 17.
      - Walter Rapp to Matles Regarding Negotiations, March 30, 1942; 18.
      - Rapp to Emspak Regarding Bonding, September 21, 1943; 19.
      - Rapp to Emspak Regarding Veterans and Dues, January 19, 1945; 20.
      - Rapp to Matles Regarding Supplies, November 23, 1945; 21.
      - Rapp to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, January 22, 1948; 22.
      - Harry Rynders to Emspak Regarding Organization, July 1, 1947; 23.
    - Local 810 Newspaper, Progress of UE 810, November 14, 1945, October 23, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Local 810 St. Louis UE News, March 3, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Local 810 Leaflets, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - "Membership Reaffirms Solidarity in UE Local 810", October 30, 1951; 1.
      - "Fines", Undated; 2.
    - Local 810 Press Releases, 1941, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - "Profits are Increasing" Regarding Organization, 1941; 1.
      - Press Release Regarding Factionalism, August 24, 1946; 2.
    - Local 810 Decca Negotiations, October 13 - November 11, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - William Sentner to Julius Emspak, Ocotber 13, 1941; 1.
      - Emspak to Sentner, November 11, 1941; 2.
    - Local 810 Amalgamation of Locals 810 and 819, January 1945 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Robert Logsden to Julius Emspak, January 15, 1945; 1.
      - Emspak to Logsden, January 23, 1945; 2.
    - Local 810 Mine Equipment Strike, May 31 - July 5, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement, May 31, 1946; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to William Sentner, June 4, 1946; 2.
      - Sentner to Emspak, June 11, 1946; 3.
      - Emspak to Sentner, July 2, 1946; 4.
      - Robert Logsden to Emspak, July 6, 1946; 5.
    - Local 810 B-L Electric Strike, May 24 - August 29, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement, May 24, 1946; 1.
      - William Sentner to David Scribner with July 9, 1946, Carl Schuddle Letter to Victor Rasche and B-L Electric Manufacturing Notice, July 10, 1946; 2.
      - Robert Logsden to James Matles, August 7, 1946; 3.
      - Julius Emspak to Logsden, August 15, 1946; 4.
      - Emspak to Logsden, August 29, 1946; 5.
    - Local 810 Johnson Tinfoil Strike, November 1946 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Robert Logsden to James Matles, November 6, 1946; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Logsden, November 8, 1946; 2.
    - Local 810 Central Mines Equipment Strike, August 4 - September 12, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Report of Strike, August 4, 1947; 1.
      - Robert Logsden to James Matles, September 12, 1947; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to Logsden, September 12, 1947; 3.
    - Local 810 Toastwell Strike, June 17 - July 11, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Robert Logsden to James Matles, June 17, 1947; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Logsden, June 25, 1947; 2.
      - Logsden to Emspak, July 10, 1947; 3.
      - Emspak to Logsden, July 11, 1947; 4.
    - Local 810 Seftor Fiber Can Inter-union Rivalry, January 1950 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Robert Logsden to James Matles, January 23, 1950; 1.
      - Logsden to Matles, January 25, 1950; 2.
    - Local 810 Correspondence, June 24, 1941 - December 17, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Robert Logsden to James Matles Regarding Negotiations, June 24, 1941; 1.
      - Victor Pasche to Nat Spero Regarding Fringe Benefits, February 28, 1945; 2.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement Regarding J. N. Dazey, April 26, 1946; 3.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement Regarding Behler Steel, May 24, 1946; 4.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement Regarding C. Nelson, May 24, 1946; 5.
      - Julius Emspak to William Sentner, May 27, 1946; 6.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement Regarding Fred Medart Manufacturing, June 20, 1946; 7.
      - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Staff Memebers, January 10, 1947; 8.
      - Logsden to Matles Regarding Mailing List, January 21, 1947; 9.
      - Logsden to Matles Regarding Johnson Metal Strike, January 9, 1950; 10.
      - 820 Program, October 1951; 11.
      - Local 810 Shops Per Capita List, December 1951; 12.
      - Logsden to Emspak Regarding Strikes, April 24, 1952; 13.
      - Otto Maschoff to Don Harris Regarding Strikes, April 1, 1954; 14.
      - Maschoff to Matles Regarding Loyd Sruggs, December 17, 1954; 15.
  - Local 811
    - Local 811 Officers Lists, August 10, 1947 - February 11, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Local 811 Incoming Correspondence, February 13, 1941 - September 2, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Julius Emspak to John Jerrell Regarding Bonding, February 13, 1941; 1.
      - Emspak to E.B. Epping Regarding Bonding, October 19, 1942; 2.
      - Emspak to Jerrell Regarding Transfers, September 1, 1943; 3.
      - Emspak to Jerrell Regarding Bonding, November 9, 1943; 4.
      - Emspak to Jerrell Regarding Veterans and Dues, September 21, 1945; 5.
      - Emspak to Jerrell Regarding Per Capita, January 17, 1947; 6.
      - Emspak to Jerrell Regarding Staff Members, September 2, 1947; 7.
      - William Sentner to Epping Regarding Finances, August 26, 1940; 8.
      - Sentner to Jerrell Regarding Constitution, August 3, 1944; 9.
    - Local 811 Outgoing Correspondence, February 1941 - November 15, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - Raymond Fowler to UE, March 11, 1944; 1.
      - John Jerrell to UE Regarding Bonding, February 1941; 2.
      - Jerrell to Julius Emspak Regarding Mailing List, September 15, 1941; 3.
      - Jerrell to Emspak Regarding Transfers, August 27, 1943; 4.
      - Jerrell to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, July 17, 1944; 5.
      - Jerrell to Emspak Regarding Progressive Cutery Separate Charter with September 2, 1947, Emspak Letter to Robert Logsdon, August 26, 1947; 6.
      - Jerrell to Emspak Regarding Officers, November 15, 1948; 7.
    - Local 810 Bonding, February 1941 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - Questionnaire, February 17, 1941; 1.
      - Form, February 24, 1941; 2.
    - Local 811 Transfer, July 1940 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - Charter Application, July 11, 1940; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to William Sentner, July 15, 1940; 2.
    - Local 811 CIO Charter Application, January 23, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Local 812 (Dubuque)
    - Local 812 (Dubuque) Officers Lists, February 8, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Local 812 (Dubuque) Newspaper, Shop Bulletin, January 6 - February 24, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Local 812 (Dubuque) Newspaper Clippings, Undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - "Opinion" Column, Undated; 1.
      - "Battery Union Gets Promise of Labor Aid," Dubuque Leader, Undated; 2.
    - Local 812 (Dubuque) Correspondence, William Wiezorek to All Employees Regarding Organization with "The UE-CIO" and Local 812 Sample Ballot, March 4, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Local 812 (Dubuque) Organization, December 1940 - January 21, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - Charter Application with History, Undated; 1.
      - Robert Logsdon to James Matles, December 1940; 2.
      - Tentative Contract, December 1940; 3.
      - William Sentner to Joseph Vejlupek, January 21, 1941; 4.
      - Bert Adams to James Payne, Undated; 5.
    - Local 812 (Dubuque) Disbanding, April 24 - July 28, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 29)
      - Julius Emspak to William Sentner, April 24, 1941; 1.
      - Sentner to Emspak, July 22, 1941; 2.
      - Emspak to Sentner, July 28, 1941; 3.
      - Robert Logsdon Report, Undated; 4.
  - Local 812 (Mason City)
    - Local 812 (Mason City) Officers Lists, October 1947 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Local 812 (Mason City) Correspondence, Julius Emspak to Daniel Vega Regarding Organization, October 21, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Local 812 (Mason City) Charter Supplies, October 20, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Local 812 (Mason City) Organization, October 21 - November 7, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 33)
      - Julius Emspak to William Sentner, October 21, 1947; 1.
      - Emspak to John Nordman, October 21, 1947; 2.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement, November 7, 1947; 3.
  - Local 813
    - Local 813 Officers Lists, March 8, 1944 - December 6, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Local 813 Officer Resolutions, September 1946 - December 2, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 35)
      - Strike, September 1945; 1.
      - Political Action Commitee, September 1946; 2.
      - Marshall Plan, December 2, 1947; 3.
    - Local 813 Membership Resolutions, July 1942 - May 16, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 36)
      - Win the War Conference, July 1942; 1.
      - Merger of Local 1002, September 15, 1942; 2.
      - Organization, September 1942; 3.
      - Sunbeam Negotiations, December 21, 1943; 4.
      - Wages, December 1943; 5.
      - Sunbeam Negotiations, December 1943; 6.
      - Servel Organization and United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, Undated; 7.
      - Wage Labor Board Negotiations, April 10, 1945; 8.
      - Foreign Policy, March 16, 1947; 9.
      - Factionalism, July 20, 1947; 10.
      - Packinghouse Workers Strikes, May 16, 1948; 11.
    - Local 813 James Payne Incoming Correspondence, April 30, 1947 - June 30, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 37)
      - Janet Barish Regarding Staff Finances, April 30, 1947; 1.
      - Joseph Dermondy Regarding Seeger and GE Contract with June 21 and 23, 1948, Dermondy Letters to G.H. Pfeif and a June 21, 1948, David Scribner Letter to R.H. Loebbe, June 24, 1948; 2.
      - Julius Emspak Regarding Strikes, October 26, 1945; 3.
      - Emspak Regarding Political Contracts with Servel, March 21, 1947; 4.
      - Emspak Regarding Per Capita, July 3, 1947; 5.
      - Emspak Regarding Servel Strikes, April 21, 1948; 6.
      - Emspak Regarding Dues and Membership, July 16, 1948; 7.
      - Emspak Regarding Dues, July 21, 1950; 8.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances and Local 805, January 30, 1951; 9.
      - Emspak Regarding UE News and Per Capita, March 6, 1951; 10.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances and Faultless Caster, August 21, 1951; 11.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, September 26, 1951; 12.
      - Emspak Regarding Servel Strikes, February 19, 1952; 13.
      - Emspak Regarding Servel Strikes, April 28, 1952; 14.
      - Emspak Regarding Stewards Meeting, November 26, 1954; 15.
      - Emspak Regarding Servel Finances, June 10, 1955; 16.
      - Emspak Regarding Servel Inter-union Rivalry, June 30, 1955; 17.
    - Local 813 James Payne Incoming Correspondence, June 4, 1947 - December 10, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 38)
      - Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Evansville Visit, June 4, 1947; 1.
      - Fitzgerald Regarding Evansville Visit, June 13, 1951; 2.
      - Fitzgerald Regarding Faultless Caster, August 8, 1951; 3.
      - Don Harris Regarding Sentner Defense Fund, July 29, 1953; 4.
      - James Matles Regarding Shop Delegates, June 2, 1947; 5.